Guide to the Manchester Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Letterbooks and Letters, Series II
  - LETTERS
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1700 Oct 21 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Diplomatic cipher, contemporary copy., 1701 Jul (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Jul 15 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Jul 18 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Prince Eugene to Alfonse Bevilacqua. (In French. Copy), 1701 Jul 19 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Jul 25 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Jul 27 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Jul 29 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Aug 1 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Aug 5 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Aug 8 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Aug 15 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Aug 19 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Aug 26 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Aug 29 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Sep 2 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Sep 5 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Sep 9 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Sep 12 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Sep 16 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - The E of M to William Blathwayt., 1701 Sep 19 (Box 18, Folder 66)